https://csn.org/privacy-policy

Child Safety Network Privacy Statement
Your personal information is confidential.
The Child Safety Network™ takes your privacy very seriously. For that reason, we have compiled and posted the following information so you can learn more about our privacy policy and how we handle any and all of your personal information collected throughout the Child Safety Network website.
What information does the Child Safety Network collect, and why?
The Child Safety Network does not request your child’s name and will never contact your child.
Additional features will be provided to our participating families in the coming months. If we learn of new laws or safety alerts that affect families in your area, we will search our database to find families that are affected by these alerts and provide that information to our members via e-mail.
We may use your contact information to send you Child Safety Network updates, monthly newsletters, or offers and resources for health, safety, nutrition and entertainment, and notification and/or reminders to check for registered sex offenders who move into your neighborhood.
We may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, other website users or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Personally identifiable information is shared with third parties if CSN determines a third party is needed to provide electronic contact on behalf of CSN, or if the third party has a valuable offer for our members, and complies with all government anti-spam regulations via e-mail marketing.
Links:
Child Safety Network contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other sites. Read the privacy statements of each website that collects identifiable information.
Security of Your Personal Information:
We understand the need for our member’s personal information to remain secure and private, and we have deployed industry-recognized safeguards that meet federal standards for the protection of your personal information, including but not limited to: monitoring for intrusion attempts; data, and Password encryption technology; firewalls and systems monitoring; and security audits and inspections. Only authorized employees have access to customer information.
Please remember that you also play a valuable part in data security. You should never share your Child Safety Network information with anyone. If you feel your identity or email has been compromised, you should take appropriate action immediately.
Copyright © 2016 The Child Safety Network. All Rights Reserved
Last updated 02.05.15
Since 1989, CSN has been making America a safer place for children to live.
Recent PostsTennessee couple who buried adopted child’s body on their property and kept kids in cages plead not guiltyTim Tebow, AG Barr announce $100M grant to fight human trafficking39 Missing Children Found, 9 Arrests Made In 'Operation Not Forgotten'
ParentingTexas students will return to school campuses this...June 19, 2020Do you Trust Artificial Intelligence to hire your babysitter?November 27, 2018Reading Aloud to Young Children Has Benefits for Behavior...May 14, 2018
image/svg+xml
AV Web Designs
AV Web Designs
Home
Terms and Conditions
Privacy
Support CSN
Contact Us
Copyright © 2019 - CSN.ORG. All Rights Reserved.
Press enter/return to begin your search
